{
    "id": "ff00e41c35ff4594b7ef63b8b59938a9",
    "title": "Expect, Wait And Hope",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. for her till 11 o’clock. Then I went home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "waited",
                "expected",
                "hoped"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "59bc24f1213c43be936e1eaa8a01a668"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was ..................... that I would win the first prize.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "expecting",
                "hoping",
                "waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f9945b5520f349e1898a70c59980b4d4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am …………………. for John.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "waiting",
                "hoping",
                "expecting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c7ce5efb038548ffac86babc93a4c797"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. she’s has got some good news.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "expect",
                "hope",
                "wait"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3944324da16144daba727dca77aecdc5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am still ..................... to hear from her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "waiting",
                "expecting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4cf5ca6bda7f4e00bc0ba73a68469ddf"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am ………………….. a phone call from him in the afternoon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "expecting",
                "waiting",
                "hoping"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ddcd6ca3c9674614a367ea02ce2d0de5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sandra is ……………….. a baby.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "waiting",
                "hoping",
                "expecting"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fea6665743414c13b40e9be8c577d5f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is hard to ……………….. for things when you are a child.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hope",
                "wait",
                "expect"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a983ed07a6614882bc0cd2da4e3696bb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. her at five, but she didn’t come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "expected",
                "waited",
                "hoped"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "38f1a2e4f959432abb185ade9af9137d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. them to turn up at eleven o’clock.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "expect",
                "wait",
                "hope"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "da07834648ea44cda1669cc6c5499557"
        }
    ]
}